[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "I was because you weren't doing her any favors by condescendingly trying to convince her that she's a victim.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "because", "you", "were", "n't", "doing", "her", "any", "favors", "by", "condescendingly", "trying", "to", "convince", "her", "that", "she", "'s", "a", "victim", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "Why would you say that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "you", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "I'll tell you why I said that, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "tell", "you", "why", "I", "said", "that", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Do you think she's stupid, Larry?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "she", "'s", "stupid", ",", "Larry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "-- to black people.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "to", "black", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Do you think she's stupid, Larry?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "she", "'s", "stupid", ",", "Larry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Racism is not a major problem in America anymore, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Racism", "is", "not", "a", "major", "problem", "in", "America", "anymore", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Ariel Castros"], "PERSON": ["George Zimmerman", "George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Do you think that Rachel Jeantel is stupid?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "Rachel", "Jeantel", "is", "stupid", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "I think that I would rather have a George Zimmerman living in my neighborhood and maybe if George Zimmerman was living my neighborhood we'd have a few fewer Ariel Castros.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "I", "would", "rather", "have", "a", "George", "Zimmerman", "living", "in", "my", "neighborhood", "and", "maybe", "if", "George", "Zimmerman", "was", "living", "my", "neighborhood", "we", "'d", "have", "a", "few", "fewer", "Ariel", "Castros", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rachel Jeantel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Could you just answer my question?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "just", "answer", "my", "question", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "You treated George Zimmerman like he's some sort of criminal.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "treated", "George", "Zimmerman", "like", "he", "'s", "some", "sort", "of", "criminal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Trayvon Martin wasn't committing crimes in that neighborhood, was he?", "question_tokens": ["Trayvon", "Martin", "was", "n't", "committing", "crimes", "in", "that", "neighborhood", ",", "was", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "It was an unfortunate incident.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "an", "unfortunate", "incident", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rachel"]}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Just out of interest, how many languages do you speak?", "question_tokens": ["Just", "out", "of", "interest", ",", "how", "many", "languages", "do", "you", "speak", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "I don't speak Ebonics as well as Rachel, if that's what you mean.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "speak", "Ebonics", "as", "well", "as", "Rachel", ",", "if", "that", "'s", "what", "you", "mean", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "And the relevance of that is what?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "relevance", "of", "that", "is", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "You don't think she's a smart cookie.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "think", "she", "'s", "a", "smart", "cookie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Do you know her educational background, Larry?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "her", "educational", "background", ",", "Larry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "I know how she presented herself on the jury.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "how", "she", "presented", "herself", "on", "the", "jury", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ":", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "Larry, do you know her educational background or not?", "question_tokens": ["Larry", ",", "do", "you", "know", "her", "educational", "background", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "People evaluate you the way -- based on the way you express yourself.", "answer_tokens": ["People", "evaluate", "you", "the", "way", "--", "based", "on", "the", "way", "you", "express", "yourself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Why don't you hire her if she's so sharp as a co-host, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "you", "hire", "her", "if", "she", "'s", "so", "sharp", "as", "a", "co-host", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Yes or no?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "or", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "I know she came across on the jury.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "she", "came", "across", "on", "the", "jury", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Why are we even talking about this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "we", "even", "talking", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Because actually I think it's relevant.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "actually", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "relevant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Where are the cameras?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "the", "cameras", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Larry.", "answer_tokens": ["Larry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "CD", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Did she sound to you like somebody you want to hire in any kid of (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "sound", "to", "you", "like", "somebody", "you", "want", "to", "hire", "in", "any", "kid", "of", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Her grades -- her grades has since slipped to two something because of the stress that she suffered understandably from the death of her friend Trayvon.", "answer_tokens": ["Her", "grades", "--", "her", "grades", "has", "since", "slipped", "to", "two", "something", "because", "of", "the", "stress", "that", "she", "suffered", "understandably", "from", "the", "death", "of", "her", "friend", "Trayvon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Did she fired the shot to try and kill him?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "fired", "the", "shot", "to", "try", "and", "kill", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "No, I think the facts in the case are clear.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "the", "facts", "in", "the", "case", "are", "clear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Did she actually claim Stand Your Ground as a defense or self-defense?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "actually", "claim", "Stand", "Your", "Ground", "as", "a", "defense", "or", "self-defense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Well, that's kind of a difficult question.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "kind", "of", "a", "difficult", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "And in the trial it was self-defense because you'd already failed in the attempt to have Stand Your Ground as a defense?", "question_tokens": ["And", "in", "the", "trial", "it", "was", "self-defense", "because", "you", "'d", "already", "failed", "in", "the", "attempt", "to", "have", "Stand", "Your", "Ground", "as", "a", "defense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Correct.", "answer_tokens": ["Correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Alan Dershowitz, I mean, on the face of it, this is a total fast, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Alan", "Dershowitz", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "on", "the", "face", "of", "it", ",", "this", "is", "a", "total", "fast", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Well, we know that there is tremendous disparity based on race in the entire criminal justice system, rates of arrests, rates of indictment, rates of conviction, rates of appellate reversal, rates of commutation, rates of release on parole.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "know", "that", "there", "is", "tremendous", "disparity", "based", "on", "race", "in", "the", "entire", "criminal", "justice", "system", ",", "rates", "of", "arrests", ",", "rates", "of", "indictment", ",", "rates", "of", "conviction", ",", "rates", "of", "appellate", "reversal", ",", "rates", "of", "commutation", ",", "rates", "of", "release", "on", "parole", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alan Dershowitz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "What I was confused by there and if you can actually clear this up, but why would she refer to Stand Your Ground, given that that was not the defense that was actually put up?", "question_tokens": ["What", "I", "was", "confused", "by", "there", "and", "if", "you", "can", "actually", "clear", "this", "up", ",", "but", "why", "would", "she", "refer", "to", "Stand", "Your", "Ground", ",", "given", "that", "that", "was", "not", "the", "defense", "that", "was", "actually", "put", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "EX", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "Because that's -- that's been on television and that's in the mind of many people in Florida.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "that", "'s", "--", "that", "'s", "been", "on", "television", "and", "that", "'s", "in", "the", "mind", "of", "many", "people", "in", "Florida", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "It would seem an absolutely perfect example of what that law is intended for?", "question_tokens": ["It", "would", "seem", "an", "absolutely", "perfect", "example", "of", "what", "that", "law", "is", "intended", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Well, not only that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "not", "only", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "What is it like in that room when you're deliberating when perhaps you don't all agree to start with about what the verdict should be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "like", "in", "that", "room", "when", "you", "'re", "deliberating", "when", "perhaps", "you", "do", "n't", "all", "agree", "to", "start", "with", "about", "what", "the", "verdict", "should", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "It's intense.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "intense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "How did you vote in that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "vote", "in", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "I voted for the death penalty.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "voted", "for", "the", "death", "penalty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "And were you frustrated that more of your colleagues didn't?", "question_tokens": ["And", "were", "you", "frustrated", "that", "more", "of", "your", "colleagues", "did", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Yes, there was definitely an element of frustration.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "there", "was", "definitely", "an", "element", "of", "frustration", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RP", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "You weren't following it as closely, obviously, as they were, but from what you've seen and heard about it, what was your view of it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "n't", "following", "it", "as", "closely", ",", "obviously", ",", "as", "they", "were", ",", "but", "from", "what", "you", "'ve", "seen", "and", "heard", "about", "it", ",", "what", "was", "your", "view", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "LLEN-COOGAN: In my opinion, the verdict ended up -- this is really difficult because I wasn't there.", "answer_tokens": ["LLEN-COOGAN", ":", "In", "my", "opinion", ",", "the", "verdict", "ended", "up", "--", "this", "is", "really", "difficult", "because", "I", "was", "n't", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "That is a failure of the prosecution, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "is", "a", "failure", "of", "the", "prosecution", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "Well, there are rules that limit testimony to relevance and after all, Trayvon Martin was not on trial.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "are", "rules", "that", "limit", "testimony", "to", "relevance", "and", "after", "all", ",", "Trayvon", "Martin", "was", "not", "on", "trial", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Do you think that either of those things were beneficial to what you went through compared to Zimmerman jurors or perhaps not so beneficial?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "either", "of", "those", "things", "were", "beneficial", "to", "what", "you", "went", "through", "compared", "to", "Zimmerman", "jurors", "or", "perhaps", "not", "so", "beneficial", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Well, definitely the lack of sequestration we would have lost some of our jurors if we had had to have been sequestered.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "definitely", "the", "lack", "of", "sequestration", "we", "would", "have", "lost", "some", "of", "our", "jurors", "if", "we", "had", "had", "to", "have", "been", "sequestered", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "What is the difference really between, say, \"The New York Times\" or the \"New York Post,\" putting that same picture on their cover as they did at the time, and \"Rolling Stone\" choosing to do it now with a much longer lead in with these kind of issues?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "difference", "really", "between", ",", "say", ",", "``", "The", "New", "York", "Times", "''", "or", "the", "``", "New", "York", "Post", ",", "''", "putting", "that", "same", "picture", "on", "their", "cover", "as", "they", "did", "at", "the", "time", ",", "and", "``", "Rolling", "Stone", "''", "choosing", "to", "do", "it", "now", "with", "a", "much", "longer", "lead", "in", "with", "these", "kind", "of", "issues", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "CC", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "LUMACKI: I just think \"Rolling Stone\" is a different type of publication.", "answer_tokens": ["LUMACKI", ":", "I", "just", "think", "``", "Rolling", "Stone", "''", "is", "a", "different", "type", "of", "publication", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "What is the difference between \"TIME\" magazine doing it when they do celebrities and serious issues and \"Rolling Stones\" do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "difference", "between", "``", "TIME", "''", "magazine", "doing", "it", "when", "they", "do", "celebrities", "and", "serious", "issues", "and", "``", "Rolling", "Stones", "''", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "NN", "''", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Well, and I actually don't think that \"Rolling Stone\" is entirely on the other side of the spectrum.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "and", "I", "actually", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "``", "Rolling", "Stone", "''", "is", "entirely", "on", "the", "other", "side", "of", "the", "spectrum", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "You read the piece, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "read", "the", "piece", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "I've read most of it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "read", "most", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Stand Your Ground"]}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "What do you think of the whole Stand Your Ground debate that's raging now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "the", "whole", "Stand", "Your", "Ground", "debate", "that", "'s", "raging", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "Well, it's a good debate to have and I'm not a fan at all of the Stand Your Ground laws.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "good", "debate", "to", "have", "and", "I", "'m", "not", "a", "fan", "at", "all", "of", "the", "Stand", "Your", "Ground", "laws", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alan Dershowitz"]}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", ":", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Would you have prosecuted Zimmerman under second-degree murder or manslaughter or not at all?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "have", "prosecuted", "Zimmerman", "under", "second-degree", "murder", "or", "manslaughter", "or", "not", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "Look, I think -- I've heard your segments with Alan Dershowitz, who -- old friend and colleague.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "'ve", "heard", "your", "segments", "with", "Alan", "Dershowitz", ",", "who", "--", "old", "friend", "and", "colleague", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 680, "question": "Do you like being the comeback kid?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "being", "the", "comeback", "kid", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "Well, I would have preferred not to have needed to be a comeback kid, but that's --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "have", "preferred", "not", "to", "have", "needed", "to", "be", "a", "comeback", "kid", ",", "but", "that", "'s", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "Have they been policed properly in your view since the huge crash?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "they", "been", "policed", "properly", "in", "your", "view", "since", "the", "huge", "crash", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 712, "question": "What does that tell you about the American public's power of forgiveness?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "that", "tell", "you", "about", "the", "American", "public", "'s", "power", "of", "forgiveness", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 713, "answer": "Well, look, I don't read too much into polls.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "read", "too", "much", "into", "polls", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "Do you want to clarify that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "to", "clarify", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "Look, I'll say only this.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "'ll", "say", "only", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]